Younis T. Hanafi

High School Senior
DOB: 5th April 2004.

Last update in 6th Feb. 2022.

Tags: #STEM_Luxor'22 #GU_CCP '21 #Logistics #Entrepreneurship_researche r #Marketing_researcher #Robotics #Content_writer

Work Experience

The Sparks Foundation

Jan 2022 - Current

STP Academy

Feb - June 2021

STEMs Guide

Jan 2020 - Current

TEDxYouth@QenaSTEM

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

TEDxYouth@LuxorSTEM

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021

NASA Space Apps Sharkya

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021

Professional Summary

Expertise in multiple programming languages such as C++, Python, PHP, JS, C#. Expertise in different frameworks like Laravel, React.js. I did numerous projects highlighted in IoT, embedded systems (Arduino), and web development projects. Enthusiastic entrepreneur, marketing researcher, and social media manager. Helped dozens of companies to stand out in the crowd to grow up their businesses on social media. Raised post engagements by 310%, people reached by 1100%, and page like by 500% After doing local/international campaigns. Scientific researcher with numerous DOIs on research gate. Currently a rising senior at Luxor STEM school, an Egyptian STEM school on a merit-based scholarship. In Addition, Georgetown University's college credits program is on a merit-based scholarship.

IoT and Computer Vision Intern.

- Building Image processing application while going through the ML career essentials.
- Getting familiar with TensorFlow and other Python Al's libraries.

Front-end web developer.

Made a full e-learning website, which helps students around the globe in learning and applying what they learned for the international curriculum of Grade 12.

Founder, CEO & Marketing director

Founded the corporation, made numerous social media campaigns, managed the team, and provided plans for the seasonal experience.

CEO & Social Media Marketing Manager

- Managed all social media platforms of TEDxYouth@QenaSTEM.
- Trained committee members

Information Technology Coordinator

- Coordinating and managing the team members towards a powerful digital standout.
- Training committee members in the creation of the TEDx Youth Luxor STEM website.

Head Of Information Technology Department

- Managing and distributing IT members in the event.
- Controlling entrance and exit traffic throughout online platforms in the pandemic.

Education

Luxor stem school

Sep 2019 - Current

Georgetown University

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

High School Diploma, Grade 12

- Founder of LCCC (Luxor Computer Coding Club).
- Member @the Math Club.

College Credit Courses, Computer Science. Grade: -A

- COSC-010 Python Track
- Summer HOYA for High school students.

Skills









Volunteering

IEEE Arabic

Oct 2020 - Current

Google Maps

Oct 2020 - Current

STEMs Guide

Jan 2020 - Current

Projects

Black-wheels

2nd Oct - 4th Oct 2021

Educational Website

May 2021 - June 2021

Acidity Preventer Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

[Project] [Research]

Burns Detector Jan 2020 - Nov 202

Game it

Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

Solar Energy: applications and uses. May, 2020 - Jun, 2020

Languages

Social Media Ambassador

- Independent & Dependent topics.
- Trends and blogging

Local Guide

- Guided +85,500 people to find their destinations.
- Helped +2,000 choosing shops and restaurants.
- +270 Contributions, +160 Answers, +40 facts checked.
- Added +30 photos, +15 reviews, +10 edits, 4 places.

Founder, CEO & Marketing director

- Helped +4,700 Students in preparatory getting prepared for STEM Schools Admissions tests.
- Provide materials in different subjects and guided students in one-to-one conversations.

Embedded Systems developer

- System for cars to recognize bumps in their way, then it slows down the speed to prevent accidents.

Front End developer

- An educational website that helps the student in learning online during the pandemics.

Embedded Systems developer, Scientific Researcher & Writer

- An Arduino system prevents soil acidity.
- Scientific research for the causes and our proposed solutions.

Al Developer

- Al Application that detects burns' degree on skins and shows the suitable treatment for patients.

Unity & C# Developer.

- A game that follows the gamification concept to help encourage children to learn.

Scientific Researcher & Writer.

- Scientific research in solar energy, sources, applications, and usages.

Arabic	English
Native Or bilingual proficiency	Professional working
French	Deutsch
Elementary proficiency	Elementary proficiency